[English subtitles are available]
[الترجمة الإنجليزية متوفرة]
[Romance with Blind Master]
[الرومانسية مع أعمى ماستر]
[Episode 13]
[الحلقة 13]
You'd better rest at home.
من الأفضل أن ترتاح في المنزل.
Besides, Mr. Ren's eyes
الى جانب ذلك ، عيون السيد رن
have recovered
تعافوا
in our treatment.
في علاجنا.
Call us if you need anything.
اتصل بنا إذا كنت بحاجة إلى أي شيء.
Thank you, doctor.
شكرا لك دكتور.
Song.
أغنية.
How is he?
كيف حاله؟
Don't worry, Miss Ruan.
لا تقلقي يا آنسة روان.
Ming's condition is very stable.
حالة مينغ مستقرة للغاية.
He'll be fine after resting at home.
سيكون بخير بعد الراحة في المنزل.
By the way, the doctor also said
بالمناسبة ، قال الطبيب أيضًا
that the tests found
التي وجدتها الاختبارات
nerve activity in Ming's eyes.
نشاط الأعصاب في عيون مينغ.
He should be able to regain his sight soon.
يجب أن يكون قادرًا على استعادة بصره قريبًا.
Really?
هل حقا؟
Song.
أغنية.
Thank you very much.
شكرا جزيلا لك.
-Have something to eat. -Okay.
-هل لديك شيء لتأكله.  -تمام.
Haoming.
هاومينغ.
When will you wake up?
متى ستستيقظ؟
Maybe
يمكن
when you wake up,
عندما تستيقظ،
you'll see me.
ستراني.
If you can wake up,
إذا كنت تستطيع الاستيقاظ ،
I'll tell you the truth.
سأقول لك الحقيقة.
I want to be with you
أريد أن أكون معك
as Ruan Qingtian.
مثل روان كينجتيان.
Xinxin.
شينجين.
Something happened.
شيء ما حصل.
I know.
أنا أعرف.
Ren Haoxuan is such a loser.
رن هاوكسوان هو مثل هذا الخاسر.
I heard that
سمعت ان
Ren Haoming's sight has been restored.
تمت استعادة رؤية Ren Haoming.
What?
لما؟
Second Young Master is completely useless.
السيد الشاب الثاني هو عديم الفائدة تماما.
But who would have thought
لكن من كان يظن
that this blind Ren Haoming
أن هذا الأعمى رين هاومينغ
would be so capable?
ستكون قادرة جدا؟
What should we do, Xinxin?
ماذا يجب أن نفعل يا شينجين؟
What do you mean?
ماذا تقصد بذلك؟
Haoming
هاومينغ
has never been our enemy.
لم يكن أبدا عدونا.
But in the past...
لكن في الماضي ...
The past is in the past.
الماضي يبقى في الماضي.
After all,
بعد كل ذلك،
isn't he
أليس هو
my fiancé?
خطيبي؟
You mean you want to
تقصد أنك تريد ذلك
let Qingtian come back?
دع كينجتيان يعود؟
How could I let her come back?
كيف يمكنني السماح لها بالعودة؟
I want her to disappear
اريدها ان تختفي
from Ren Haoming's side.
من جانب رن هاومينغ.
If that happens,
إذا حدث ذلك،
when Ren Haoming wakes up,
عندما يستيقظ رن هاومينغ ،
I'll be the first person he sees.
سأكون أول شخص يراه.
I'll be the one who's been by his side,
سأكون الشخص الذي كان بجانبه ،
and the one who he loves.
ومن يحب.
No, Xinxin.
لا ، شينجين.
Is there any other way?
هل هناك أي طريقة أخرى؟
Are you worried about her?
هل أنت قلق عليها؟
I...
أنا...
I didn't mean that.
لم أقصثد ذلك
I don't think it's necessary.
لا أعتقد أنه ضروري.
Besides,
بجانب،
Qingtian
كينجتيان
is your sister too.
هي اختك ايضا.
All of you only care about Ruan Qingtian.
كلكم يهتمون فقط بـ Ruan Qingtian.
What's so good about her?
ما الجيد فيها؟
Isn't it just because
أليس هذا لمجرد
she was the one who was brought back?
كانت هي التي أعيدت؟
What about me?
ماذا عني؟
I have nothing.
ليس لدي أي شيء.
I got nothing.
لم اتحصل على شيء.
These belong to me in the first place.
هذه تخصني في المقام الأول.
Mom.
أم.
Didn't you say
لم تقل
you would always
كنت دائما
be on my side?
كن بجانبي؟
Yes.
نعم.
I'm on your side.
أنا بجانبك.
Put her in the car. Let's go.
ضعها في السيارة.  هيا بنا.
Haoming.
هاومينغ.
Anyone there?
أي شخص هناك؟
Hello?
مرحبًا؟
If you don't want to be gagged,
إذا كنت لا تريد أن تكون مكمماً ،
then shut up.
حسنا فلتصمت.
Who are you?
من أنت؟
What do you want?
ماذا تريد؟
Listen to me.
استمع لي.
Calm down.
اهدأ.
This is illegal, you know?
هذا غير قانوني ، هل تعلم؟
You'll go to jail
ستذهب إلى السجن
for at least ten years.
لمدة عشر سنوات على الأقل.
Don't come over.
لا تأتي.
I beg you.
أرجوك.
Don't come over!
لا تأتي!
Help!
يساعد!
Who are you?
من أنت؟
Who sent you here?
من أرسلك إلى هنا؟
Eat it if you're hungry.
تناوله إذا كنت جائعا.
Miss Ruan hasn't been back for two days.
لم تعد الآنسة روان منذ يومين.
That's not right.
هذا غير صحيح.
Miss Ruan.
ملكة جمال روان.
Where have you been?
أين كنت؟
I thought something happened to you.
اعتقدت أن شيئا ما حدث لك.
Something happened at home.
شيء ما حدث في المنزل.
You can leave now.
يمكنك المغادرة الآن.
Okay.
تمام.
Ren Haoming.
رن هاومينغ.
From now on, the person by your side
من الآن فصاعدا ، الشخص بجانبك
is me.
هو انا.
Haoming.
هاومينغ.
You're awake.
انت مستيقظ.
Take it slow.
على مهلك.
Xinxin.
شينجين.
You can see now?
ترون الآن؟
That's great!
هذا جيد!
I miss you so much.
أفتقدك كثيرًا.
You've been
لقد كنت
taking care of me all this time.
يعتني بي كل هذا الوقت.
Thank you.
شكرًا لك.
You were in a coma for half a month.
كنت في غيبوبة لمدة نصف شهر.
I was really scared.
كنت خائفة حقا.
I thought
اعتقدت
I would lose you.
سأفقدك.
It won't happen again.
لن يحدث ذلك مرة أخرى.
I feel a little dizzy.
أشعر بقليل من الدوار.
I want to rest for a little longer.
أريد أن أستريح لفترة أطول قليلاً.
I'll get you a glass of water.
سأحضر لك كوب ماء.